export const QuizData = [
    {
        question: "Which country hosted the 2022 Winter Olympics?",
        options: ["South Korea", "China", "Russia", "Japan"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "What global health crisis emerged in late 2019?",
        options: ["Zika Virus", "Ebola Outbreak", "COVID-19", "SARS"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Which company became the world's first trillion-dollar company?",
        options: ["Apple", "Amazon", "Microsoft", "Google"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Which environmental activist inspired the global climate strike movement?",
        options: ["Greta Thunberg", "Malala Yousafzai", "Emma Watson", "Nelson Mandela"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Which country's team won the UEFA European Championship in 2020?",
        options: ["Italy", "France", "Portugal", "Germany"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What historic agreement was reached between Israel and the United Arab Emirates in 2020?",
        options: ["Camp David Accords", "Oslo Accords", "Abraham Accords", "Suez Canal Treaty"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Which space agency successfully landed the Perseverance rover on Mars in 2021?",
        options: ["NASA", "ESA", "Roscosmos", "ISRO"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Which cryptocurrency gained significant attention for its rapid price increase?",
        options: ["Ethereum", "Ripple (XRP)", "Litecoin", "Bitcoin"],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "Who became the first female Vice President of the United States?",
        options: ["Hillary Clinton", "Kamala Harris", "Nancy Pelosi", "Elizabeth Warren"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Which country recently faced a military coup leading to the overthrow of Aung San Suu Kyi's government?",
        options: ["Thailand", "Cambodia", "Vietnam", "Myanmar (Burma)"],
        answer: 4
    }
];
